Uh oh, uh oh, uh oh, oh no no
哦噢,哦哦,哦哦,哦,不不
I look and stare so deep in your eyes
我深深地凝视着你的瞳孔
I touch on you more and more every time
我触摸你越来越多的每一次
When you leave I'm begging you not to go
当你离开我求你不要走
Call your name two or three times in a row
叫你的名字连续两三次
Such a funny thing for me to try to explain.How I'm feeling and my pride is the one to blame
我尝试着向你表白这般有趣的事情  我感受到是我的造成的错
Just how your love your doing no one else can.Got me looking so crazy right now, your love's.Got me looking so crazy right now (in love).Got me looking so crazy right now, your touch.Got me looking so crazy right now (your touch)
你的爱已没有什么可以给予的了  现在让我看上去很疯狂,你的爱  现在让我看上去很疯狂(爱)  现在让我看上去很疯狂,你的触摸  现在让我看上去很疯狂(触摸)
Got me hoping you'll page me right now, your kiss.Got me hoping you'll save me right now.Looking so crazy in love's.Got me looking, got me looking so crazy in love
给我希望 告诉我现在给我一个吻  我希望你现在就救我  寻找爱的如此疯狂  让我看看,让我如此疯狂的爱